Sheryl Edery

Raanana | +972 586 676 196 | sheryledery@icloud.com Github | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer experienced in Python and JavaScript based programming. My background is in sales and event planning, which have given me valuable project management skills. I pride myself on being efficient, independent and always striving to improve my skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, JavaScript, OOP, SQL, Flask, Django, HTML, CSS

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

DOMination - Github / Demo

A simple game for children using JavaScript, DOM

Findme - Demo

Address book using Python and Tkinter tools

EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative
Green Eco Energie

Tel Aviv, Israel
06/2020 - 08/2020

- Sold energy saving products
- Ecological system home equipment consultancy
- · Managed contracts, appointments and client eligibility
- Increased my sales rate by 200% every week

Event Planner and Organizer

GOséminaire

Paris, France 02/2020 - 06/2020

- Organized business seminar for large companies
- Sourced atypical locations according to customer needs
- Spot the best places, arrange to find availability
- Mastery of computer tools (Google Map, CRM)
- Good speech and good relationship with customers
- Exchanges in French and English with customers

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel Aviv, Israel

High School Diploma
Maimonide Mikve Israel

2017-2020

- Graduated with honors
- Economics & Social Studies focus

LANGUAGES

French - native speaker, Hebrew - fluent, English - fluent, Spanish - beginner

Tel Aviv. Israel

09/2020 - 01/2021